<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on OkraHealth</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on OkraHealth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 12:24:47 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>OkraHealth, under the MIT License, provides interpretable health analytics for any software using Git version control. Software development is often a complex task which is dependent on the health of additional software libraries. Understanding the health of our software and its dependencies has implications for maintainability, cost, and security.
OkraHealth makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Django Rest Framework Pandas Protocol Buffers SQLAlchemy  OkraHealth is ideal for software developers, cyber security professionals, and businesses seeking to better understand their software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Documentation for OkraHealth is available using the following links:
 [Okra-API]()  RESTful API for consuming Okra software health analytics  Okra-Core  Library used for generating health analytics and data pipeline   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Origin of OkraHealth and Pre-Alpha Release</title>
      <link>/blog/starting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 12:24:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/starting/</guid>
      <description>OkraHealth came out of a project-based course I took while finishing my MS in Data Science at Northeastern University. DS 6050 - Expeditions in Data Science was being piloted as an alternative to the core capstone class DS 5500, Information Visualization, in Spring 2019 only. The DS 6050 course encouraged students to solve real-world data science problems by applying the skills they obtained in previous classes of their Data Science program.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>